## Trevan Lawade Young Software Developer 910-797-5164

trevanyoung@gmail.com https://github.com/trevanyoung

Clearance: Top Secret

I am a Signal Intelligence Analyst and Software Developer with over 8 years of intelligence experience with a focus in Geo-Location. This includes 5 years of military service with multiple combat deployments as a tactical SIGINT operator and 4 years as a Geo-Location operator. Currently enrolled in a 6 month full time Full Stack Development bootcamp at the Nashville Software School in Tennessee.

## Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Bootstrap, ReactStrap jQuery

Database Tools: JSON

Certifications
Comptia A+

## Experience

Full Stack Developer, Nashville Software School, January 2019-Current

Full time software development bootcamp that concentrates on Full Stack Development essentials and problem solving. Course is divided into 3 months of Front End Development, and 3 months of Back End development that is executed in a simulated company environment with Scrum methodology. Hands-on application of OOP fundamentals in both group and individual projects. Single-page web application development using HTML, JavaScript, React and CSS/Reactstrap. Application design through wire framing and white boarding dependencies Task Automation with Grunt, Browserify, and NPM. Project management with Github.

Level 1 Technician, Unisys, March 2018-December 2018

Provides Tier 1 Information Technology support of hardware, systems, and applications for Microsoft employees via inbound calls and emails. Guides user through the hardware and software configuration to resolve issues. Remotes into end users computer if necessary. Utilizes Active Directory to manager user accounts. Assists with troubleshooting network connection problems to allow remote employees to access the corporate network via virtual private networks for secure data transmissions.

Geo-Location Operator, National Security Agency Jul 2014-Jan 2018

Operated collection systems to provide near real time intelligence to tactical commanders and national level customers including special operation forces. Applies advanced geo-location analysis techniques to targets of interest to facilitate support of given missions. Advises the customer on guidelines for optimal usage of collection systems.

Customer Service Representative, T-Mobile March 2014-July 2014

Responsible for answering incoming phone calls from T-Mobile customers. Duties included educating customers about their services and devices, assisting them with billing issues and placing orders for new equipment. Conducted troubleshooting with customers for devices such as cell phones, tablets, and WiFi hotspots that used Android, iOS, and Windows operating systems.

Signal Intelligence Analyst, United States Army June 2009-March 2014

Collected and analyzed VHF communications with direction finding to provide on the ground reporting of enemy operations and to aid the tactical mission of maneuver units on the ground resulting in their mission success. Prepared intelligence reports and briefed ground force commanders. Operated automated data processing equipment for signal intelligence collection. Maintained analytical working aids and databases to support target collection. Performed maintenance on surveillance systems and or communication equipment. Deployed to combat environments and supported conventional Infantry and Special Operation Forces.

Education

Western Governors University, Information Technology: 2017-2018

Nashville Software School, Full Stack Development Bootcamp: Jan 2019- Current